# Jenny Dinh

5483 Danbury Circle, Lake in the Hills, IL, 60156 (224) 622-7111 • jenny.p.dinh@gmail.com • www.github.com/jdinh3 www.linkedin.com/in/jennifer-dinh • https://jdinh3.github.io/react-portfolio

# **Summary:**

A full-stack web developer with several years of work experience in Audio Engineering and Sales management who is eager to learning new technical skills and methods. Leveraged strong teamwork ethic and problem-solving skills to successfully create Full Stack applications in an agile environment. Enjoys using creativity and contributing new ideas to team environments.

## **Education:**

Georgia Institute of Technology • Full Stack Web Development Certificate

A 12-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills for Full Stack Web Development using Javascript. • Completion: June 2021

Columbia College Chicago • Chicago, IL • Graduation: May 2017 • Cumulative GPA: 3.8/4.0

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) in Audio Engineering • Minor: Management

**Huntley High School • Huntley, IL • Graduation: June 2013** 

#### **Technical Skills:**

HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, React JS, JQuery, Node JS, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handlebars JS, Bootstrap, JQuery, APIs, Node JS, Insomnia, Git, GitHub

# **Projects:**

# **Employee Directory**

Deployed Site: https://jdinh3.github.io/employee-directory/ • GitHub Repository: https://github.com/jdinh3/employee-directory/

- A searchable and sortable directory of employees.
- Technologies used: React JS, Random User API, Bootstrap

## **Fitness Tracker**

Deployed Site: https://stark-refuge-78989.herokuapp.com/?id=6096d3b98d88890015c4f1a4

GitHub Repository: <a href="https://github.com/jdinh3/fitness-tracker">https://github.com/jdinh3/fitness-tracker</a>

- A web application designed for users to document and track their workouts
- Technologies used: MongoDB, Mongoose, Express, Bootstrap

# **Work Experience:**

Aerotek • Engineering Recruiter • Schaumburg, IL • October 2020 – March 2021

- Called and screened 30+ qualified candidates on a daily basis for various engineering roles
- Interviewed 5 candidates weekly and called references for each candidate

PSAV • Sales Manager • Loews Vanderbilt Hotel • June 2019 – March 2020

- Consulted 6+ clients at a time on audio visual needs for their conferences.
- Brought in an average annual revenue of \$1.9 million
- Received a cumulative Customer Survey score of 9 or higher

Sales Coordinator • Gaylord Opryland Resort • June 2018 – June 2019

• Consulted 6+ clients at a time on audio visual needs for their meetings and created proposals under \$5,000

AV Technician • Loews Chicago Hotel • November 2016 – June 2018

- Set up audio, video and lighting equipment for 4+ meetings or conferences daily
- Troubleshooted and fixed technical problems on-site.